WE DON'T NEED APPS.
ENROLL MORE SLUTS LIKE CHLOE.
MY ATTENTION SPAN IS SHIT.
CAN I GET SOME ADD MEDS?
They're mocking us,
not reaching out for help.
I really don't see the point of the app.
Or my work here.
I see. Well, it's only the first day.
We need to be patient.
Right.
Omar, I respect your decision
to stop going to therapy.
I just want to remind you
that you still have a long way to go.
You don't need to go back on your meds,
and you don't need to self-medicate.
I'm here to help you.
Hi, Mateo. How are you?
Listen, I just need
a break from our sessions.
That's all. But thanks for your concern.
- Samu!
What did he do to you?
Samu?
Samu…
Hi.
- What's that?
- Your suit. It's for the horse race.
Here. It's yours.
What? No way.
I'd like to give this to you as a friend.
Yeah, sure. Just like my tuition.
No, Iván. No way.
You need to wear a suit to attend.
No worries. I wasn't planning on going.
I can't afford it.
Joel…
I'd love to go with you
and have a good time together.
How do you know my size?
I don't. I took a guess.
Right.
Well, I'd better try it on.
I don't know if I trust your judgment.
I'm going to the locker room.
Coming?
You can tell me if it's a good fit.
You good?
Me? Yeah.
I'm good.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
- Fine.
- What would be wrong?
Hello.
Omar?
- Iván!
- Wow!
- Long time no see.
- How's it going?
What are you doing here?
I see you've met my boyfriend.
You guys know each other?
So? What are you up to?
Nothing. Just…
I'm trying on a suit for a charity race.
What about you? What are you doing here?
CHARITY HORSE RACE
- Morning, Roberta. Is everything okay?
- Good morning.
I know you ordered the shooting.
Relax. I'm not out for revenge.
I'm here to warn you.
Leave Dídac out of this.
He stays at school no matter what.
Understood?
But I won't allow him
to keep dating my daughter.
I don't like it either,
but it's their life.
I know.
It's not the most important thing,
but it still really matters.
True. But there's nothing we can do.
You've been through a lot.
Now your body's telling you
it needs more time.
That's all, okay?
Don't worry.
How are my two cuties doing?
Can I have a moment alone
with my daughter, sweetie?
See you later.
Why are you here?
I came to finalize plans
for the race with Virginia.
And to bring you a little something.
I want the whole racetrack
to know who my daughter is.
I know a bribe when I see one.
Which of our horses do you want to use?
Not happening.
- Baby-
- Absolutely not.
- She's our best mare.
- That's why she can't race, Mom.
Think about it.
It's dangerous. She's too old.
The trip here will stress her out.
Can't you see?
She's our horse.
How can you treat her like that?
See? This is why you're not cut out
for the family business.
Horses are part of the business too.
And business comes first, right?
Can we stop with the negativity, please?
- Do it for me.
- No, I'm out. I'm not going to the race.
I swear to God,
if anything happens to her,
you'll never see me again
in your fucking life.
Hey.
Didn't you go to school?
No, I wasn't feeling well.
Why are you home?
I came to grab some files for Virginia
for the live stream of the race.
You're gonna get them and go?
Yeah.
Hey, you know what?
I'll email her the files and call later.
That way, I can stay and take care of you.
You can't skip a meeting with her.
She's my principal.
Besides, I was just leaving.
- Weren't you feeling sick?
- Yeah, I was.
I was feeling sick.
But I'm okay now.
I just needed to skip first period.
I'm fine, really.
Are you sure?
I'll get dressed.
NEW MESSAGE
I NEED TO BE ALONE, BUT I CAN'T.
I'M FEELING TRAPPED.
Sara.
Yes?
Your gym class evaluation grade
was disappointing.
I know. I'm sorry.
I'll make up for it.
You seem out of it.
What's that rash on your arm?
I have allergies.
Those must be some strong allergies.
What are you allergic to?
A lot. A lot of things.
I have to go, Jessica.
Or I'll be late to class.
Why did you accept the internship
if you hate Las Encinas so much?
Well, I need the money,
and it'll look good on my résumé.
Are you here to keep tabs on me?
To protect you.
I trust you, Joel.
- But this place is dangerous.
- Here we go.
Can't you see this is unfair?
Look, Omar. I'm not you, okay?
And I'm not one of your school friends.
I'm Joel, and I deserve this opportunity.
I'm just concerned.
But I don't need a father.
I need a boyfriend
who can be happy for me,
who trusts me, who gives me space,
and who isn't a clingy control freak.
For fuck's sake.
KICK DÍDAC AND THE MAFIA
OUT OF OUR SCHOOL!!!
Iván.
If the fact
that I'm in a relationship bothers you,
I can transfer to another school.
Paying for your tuition is the only thing
that's made me happy lately.
I'm still okay with being just friends.
So are we still on for the race?
Yeah, of course.
Omar's coming too, right?
I don't think so. He's too busy.
What's up?
Sonia.
Thank you for not telling anyone
that I leaked the video.
Is this reverse psychology?
Want me to spread the word
so you get more attention?
I'm not happy to be here,
and I took it out on the wrong person.
So you're a real person with feelings.
Friends? School friends?
Casual acquaintances?
Hey, is it true
that the soccer player's son is bi?
Seriously? Are you planning
your next sex tape or what?
Okay. I'll take that as a yes.
With him, I'd go for a cute video.
You know? Showing off
my rich, sexy, handsome boyfriend.
And an orphan too.
No mother-in-law.
It's like hitting the lottery.
- You make it seem like he's a trophy.
- No, not a trophy.
The trophy.
Wow. Just when I was starting
to think you were cool.
You can try your luck,
but it won't be easy.
Wanna bet?
I live for challenges.
Nothing turns me on like a tough one.
Another way to seek external validation.
I'm blown away
by your emotional stability.
What's going on?
I'm sick of people staring at me.
I know.
Want to skip class?
Let me introduce you to Amazona.
Hi, Amazona. How are you?
Hi, sweetie.
- I didn't know you liked horses.
- I love them.
I grew up with them in Ibiza.
She's my favorite.
My mom and I adopted her together.
My mom wanted to give her to me,
but I said no so she could have two moms.
Actually, she helped bring
my mom and I closer.
Until she made her race.
That's when the problems started.
I'm very much against her racing.
But you know, when it comes to business,
Roberta doesn't care about anything else.
During her last race, she fell.
It's a miracle nothing happened to her.
I was scared to death.
If you don't want her to race again,
we could kidnap her
and take her to a sanctuary,
without telling anyone.
But we have to do it before the race.
You need a pass to enter the stables.
As owner, your mom should have one, right?
Yeah.
Let's find a way to get it.
Thank you.
Hi, everyone.
We're at this incredible racetrack,
ready to experience
the Las Encinas Charity Horse Race.
And it's all for a good cause.
Supporting scholarships
for exchange programs
between the Excellentia Academic
Global League's top schools
in Europe and Africa.
Don't miss it.
We'll give you the full rundown.
We should go back to doing
the live streams together on camera.
Our viewers notice everything.
But you do you.
I'm gonna look for Virginia.
Enjoy yourselves. I'll catch you later.
Hi. How's it going?
You look gorgeous.
The ambassador made it after all.
His wife has really put on weight.
- I'm borrowing your stable pass.
- What for?
I want to give Amazona a kiss.
No, baby. You'll just make her nervous.
You can go later. Don't be a pain.
- How are you doing, Dídac?
- I'm okay. You?
I read some comments
about you and your family on the app.
Yeah, there are a few.
But that's okay.
Well, if you ever need
to talk about anything,
your feelings, your classmates,
your family…
My family?
Your family or anything else.
I'm here for you, okay? I won't judge you.
Okay. Thank you.
What the hell are you doing here, Pau?
I was invited. I'm your family.
Well, I want you to get out of here.
You never looked at me with such disgust.
Go, please.
You're making a mistake, kiddo.
- This stuff gets you buzzed in no time.
- Yeah.
- I'll get some more.
- Okay.
- I'm so sorry about what happened to you.
- Excuse me?
The hit-and-run.
And the thing with your father.
The moms at school talk. You know.
I just wanted to let you know
that I'm so sorry.
Thanks, ma'am.
Iván, isn't it?
Iván.
What a beautiful name.
I've always liked it.
I'm Carmen.
Leave formalities aside.
Pleased to meet you.
How's everything going?
Not great, as you know.
Oh, shit. I'm sorry.
- I put my foot in my mouth.
- It's okay. Look.
My friend is waiting for me…
Your father was a great guy.
Did you know him?
From the press.
And I know what he did for you guys.
What do you mean?
Gay people.
He's with God now.
God loves you. Don't forget that.
Wow. You're the spitting image
of your father.
I'd say you're even better looking.
Mom, how about you hang out
with guys your age?
I'll see you around.
- Of course. Bye.
- Bye.
Mom, he could be your son.
- What?
- What do you mean?
I saw how you smiled at him.
- Cute, rich. Should I spell it out?
- I wasn't hitting on him.
Fine. But I won't let you
embarrass me here too.
Stay away from him.
That's not what I had in mind.
And even if it was,
he's gay, like his dad.
Just stay away from him, okay?
- Okay.
- Bye.
I don't care what we said.
We're working for free?
- It's a collaboration.
- Okay. Fine.
No.
Thanks.
Sorry about the misunderstanding.
Godddammit!
- What's wrong?
- That bitch Virginia!
- Keep your voice down.
- She won't pay us for the live stream.
- You knew. She asked me as a favor.
- And you volunteered?
We're strapped for cash, damn it!
We can't afford rent.
- Why didn't you tell me?
- I did.
I told you if we broke up,
you'd wreck the fucking account.
I said if we weren't a happy couple,
we'd keep losing followers
and brands would forget about us.
There you go.
You need to know that your outbursts
have consequences, you fucking brat.
Sorry. My mom can be annoying sometimes.
No, don't worry. She wasn't bothering me.
You look uncomfortable.
You recognized me from the video, right?
What video?
Come on. Haven't you seen it?
No.
I'll send it to you.
Actually, I'll send you
an even better one.
- There you go.
- Thanks.
Don't mention it.
Bye.
I couldn't find you.
What? I took so long
that you had to order yourself?
Here you go.
- Thanks.
- You're welcome.
Cheers.
Excuse me.
No sign of my cousin.
My folks will be pissed if he skips this.
COMMUNITY CENTER #STAYING
No. Today, it's the uniform.
Tomorrow, something else.
Yeah, I can't stand uniforms
and a lot of our rules.
Said the domesticated sheep.
The best way to change the system
is from within.
Really? How?
Shooting off an angry tweet?
Or pinning a ribbon on your lapel?
My buddy from the court just called.
The riot police will be back tonight.
Those bastards.
I can stop the eviction.
Eric, listen to me.
You? How?
Put your suit on.
Come with us, and I'll show you how.
I came out to my parents,
and they kicked me out of the house.
That stuff still happens, huh?
I slept in parks for a while.
I ate wherever I could.
Until I came to Madrid
and asked for help at an association.
Omar was working there.
And without knowing each other,
out of the blue,
he asked me to move in with him.
I don't know.
I always thought that…
we were meant for each other.
Besides, we were both
going through it when we met.
I was coping with being kicked out,
while Omar was battling depression.
I don't know why.
He never wanted to talk about it.
It was so huge
that he nearly did something crazy.
But, hey.
We pushed through it together
and fell in love along the way.
Though now, I don't know
if it was love or if we needed each other.
When did you meet?
Almost a year ago. Why?
Samu.
Who's Samu? His ex?
His best friend.
He also attended Las Encinas.
He died in Omar's arms.
Omar?
You should've told me
about your friend Samu.
The worst part is,
I could have prevented it.
If only I hadn't pushed him away…
If I'd watched out for him…
Damn it.
Come on. Come here.
It's okay.
There.
All bets are now final.
She won't let go of her bag.
The sixth and last race
will begin in 30 minutes.
Goddammit.
Nico, how are you?
Son, your cousin is out of control.
You need to accept that.
It's best for everyone.
Look who's here.
Let's go.
That's my mom. She's a judge.
And the best example
that the system can change from within.
DID YOU LIKE MY VIDEO?
How's your challenge going?
Almost got him.
How's yours?
I saw how you look at Nico.
So, she dodged your kiss?
Then ran off to the dance floor.
Yeah, but I don't want to get hurt.
No one else makes me feel as good.
Why don't you apologize?
I try to play it cool,
but I can't get over him.
I hear you.
I'll be right back.
You're gonna have to play it cool.
He's coming over.
Don't bail on me now.
I can't be alone with him.
Hello.
- Hi.
Well, I'll be right back.
Chloe, don't go.
Iván, thanks for telling Joel about Samu.
And for helping us out.
We patched things up.
By the way, I heard that Patrick
is the main suspect in your hit-and-run.
You know as well as I do that it's absurd.
He'd never do that to you.
Just in case you needed a reminder.
Hello, gorgeous.
Hello.
You seem bummed out.
You left me on read.
So, you didn't like the video?
Yeah, I liked it.
Iván, look,
I've seen that sad look before.
But you know what?
I'm the best at curing broken hearts.
I mean, look…
A little bit of this…
and you won't even remember their name.
"I love bondage."
"I get so turned on
when my wife whips me."
"Oh, yeah. He gets so into it."
"I just smack him, bam, bam, bam!
And he begs me for more."
Shit. They're looking at us.
I'm starving.
I'll be back. Don't move.
Excuse me, can I have this?
Thank you.
Hey, it's actually good.
I really missed this.
Hanging out with you.
I wish I could press rewind
and undo the pain I caused you.
Right. But you can't.
How can I make it up to you?
And make you feel better?
Let's play a little, okay?
For a Brazilian guy,
there's not a lot of samba in you.
Maybe we should stop.
It happens sometimes.
Look, close your eyes
and just enjoy yourself.
Okay… let's stop.
I'm not feeling it right now. Sorry.
Wow, so you are going to be
my biggest challenge.
Chloe, open the door.
Mom?
Open up. I need to talk to you.
- I can't right now, Mom.
- I said open the door, Chloe!
No.
Iván.
Can you try
not to be jealous of me for once?
That's not it.
That boy isn't right for you.
Trust me, Chloe.
- Fuck you!
- Hey! Don't talk to me like that.
Wait! Hold on!
Chloe, listen to me, please.
Chloe, stop!
Chloe, please!
Chloe, I said stop!
What? What are you doing?
- He's your brother.
- What?
Wow, Mom, you're…
You're so fucking crazy,
you'd say anything to win.
- That's it, isn't it?
- No, I'm not lying.
That's why we're here.
For reasons beyond our control,
the last race has been suspended.
- What happened?
- What's wrong?
- I'm sorry.
- What?
- She's been poisoned.
We couldn't do anything to save her.
What the hell are you doing here?
Get out of here. Get lost.
Mom…
Who do you think did this to Amazona?
No…
Your brother won't stop
until he ruins our lives.
Fuck…
Dídac.
Dídac, what's wrong?
I'm sick of my family.
Those fucking murderers.
Nothing's wrong with me.
Any problems at home?
I know about the drama
with your boyfriend.
In fact, millions of people know.
And I see through his act
of crying so you'll take him back.
I know his type. He's a textbook case.
Sorry, but stay out of my life.
I went through something very similar.
What are you talking about?
I'm fine.
No issues at home or anywhere else.
I also thought there was no way out.
But there is.
However, you have to look for it yourself,
not wait for it to appear.
But for that to happen…
I have to disappear.
That's what everyone says.
So, until we see each other again…
I love you.
I love you so much, Iván.
I always have, and I always will.
DO YOU WANT TO DELETE THIS FILE?
The person who hit me
must have been at the masked ball.
I didn't see anything.
I'm sorry.
You want us to take him in?
As long as he's living alone,
he'll keep obsessing over it.
He won't stop until he finds the truth.
If he's here,
we'll have him under control.
But leaving my house like that…
What will I do with it?
Rent it out.
Or sell it.
Iván, that house is a trap.
As long as you live there,
the walls will close in on you
and your ghosts will haunt you.
Your dad, Patrick, the hit-and-run…
You'll never move on.
No. This is our home.
We're gonna lose it anyway, right?
If we bring in a third person
who has no problem paying rent,
we'd keep the apartment
and look for new clients
to help us get back on our feet.
Trust me, babe.
You're right.
But if I leave my house…
where will I live?
SARAUL ARE FAKE AF
Why aren't you dressed? You'll be late.
I'm leaving school.
I just mean,
I don't want to make you suffer.
Would you really do that for me?
Of course.
Look, you…
are my top priority.
I'm the one who has a problem.
And I'm the one who'll quit my job.
But… what about your résumé?
And the money?
What money? I get paid peanuts.
And the app doesn't work.
It's only used for trolling.
If I want to get over my trauma,
I need to let you do your thing.
And stay away from that school.
Thank you.
I promise you I won't change.
Luis, can we talk?
Yeah, sure.
MY LIFE IS HELL.
I CAN'T SEE A WAY OUT.
I NEED TO STOP BEING A BURDEN.
Omar, what's wrong?
You see?
I knew we'd get a cry for help eventually.
And we'll be there for them.
I'M HERE TO LISTEN TO YOU
AND HELP YOU WITH WHATEVER YOU NEED.
TALK TO ME.
Subtitle translation by: Toni Navarro,
Meredith Cannella